{
    "id": "6edb9935da0140c3be54ef7623b1feb1",
    "title": "Few vs. Little Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2bcc95fd88204ac2bcdd34f4c36f4b52",
            "title": "Few vs. Little",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She seemed the .............................. concerned.",
                    "description": "The least concerned means not concerned at all. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "least",
                        "fewest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has got very ................................ friends.",
                    "description": "Very few indicates a very small number. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "less",
                        "a few",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has got only ............................... friends.",
                    "description": "Use a few after only.",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "a few",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................. students attended the class today than yesterday.",
                    "description": "A comparative form is required here. Use fewer with plural nouns and less with uncountable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "Fewer",
                        "less",
                        "little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I now have .............................. problems than I used to.",
                    "description": "Use fewer with plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "fewer",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "'She is upset with you.' 'I couldn't care .................................'",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "less",
                        "least"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He paid ................................ attention to what I was saying.",
                    "description": "Little attention means hardly any attention. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "least",
                        "fewest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He finished the job with ................................ difficulty.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "few",
                        "least"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The task was ............................... difficult than I thought.",
                    "description": "Less is the comparative form of little. A comparative word is required before than. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "less",
                        "least"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was the .................................... popular among them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "less",
                        "least"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has ................................ concern for name or fame.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "few",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I know very .................................... people in this town.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "fewer",
                        "fewest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}